Quercio?
Yes.Q-U-E-R-C-I-O.Quercio.
对. Q-U-E-R-C-I-O. Quercio.
Oh yes,here it is.
Oh yes, 它在这呢
Excuse me, Are you Tony Quercio?
打搅一下, 你是Tony Quercio吗?
Yes I am.
对, 我是的
Are you here for the American Library Association Conference?
你来这里  为了美国图书馆协会会议吗?
Yes.
对
My name's Barbara Seaton.
我的名字是Barbara Seaton.
-You're Barbara Seaton!  Yes!
-你是Barbara Seaton!  -对.
Barbara Seaton,of the New York Library?
Barbara Seaton, 纽约图书馆的?
-Tony Quercio,Watson's Bookstores?  -Yes.
-Tony Quercio, Watson书店?  -对
How do you do?
你好
It's nice to meet you finally.
很高兴见到你  终于.
Nice to meet you.
-很高兴见到你.
I'm sorry.
抱歉
That's all right.
没关系
Mr.Quercio.Room 412.
Quercio先生. 房间412
412. Great.
412. 好嘞.
Carl? Room 412,please.
Carl? 房间412, 请.
Well,I'll talk to you later,Barbara.
那个, 我之后再跟你聊, Barbara.
Of course. Bye now.
当然了. 拜拜 现在.
And welcome to Boston!
并且欢迎来到波士顿!